fashionfling.com 2012-01-19

# Fashion Fling - Reviews, Giveaways, Coupons, New Products, Coupon Codes, Blog: Privacy Policy

We value and respect our visitors privacy. That is the reason why we included this privacy policy to make sure that your privacy is not being violated. If you have any questions concerning our Privacy Policy, please do not hesitate to ask!

 _ **What kind of information does Fashion Fling collect?  
**_

The only information we may gather is your name and home address if you're a winner of any of our contests. We will not share this information with anyone (unless the sponsor is sending the prize) and we will not save any of your information after your prize has been sent.

We 

_**WILL NOT**_

share, sell, rent, market any of your personal information to another party.

 _ **Stores Privacy Policy**_

All merchants and advertisers have their own privacy policy, and we advise you to review their privacy policy before purchasing or subscribing to anything.

 _ **Children  
**_

We do not collect personal information from children under 13 without appropriate parental notice and consent. Note: Visit <http://business.ftc.gov/privacy-and-security/children%E2%80%99s-online-privacy> for information from the Federal Trade Commission about protecting children's privacy online.

 **Advertising:**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.
